[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[CLARK] My most vivid memories
are of the days when my life changed.
I remember coming to this Earth feeling
the sun on my face for the first time.
[MARTHA] Oh, my God.
Jonathan. It's a baby boy.
[JONATHAN]
Hold on, Martha.
[CLARK]
Hearing the voices of my parents.
My mother called me
their greatest surprise.
And boy, there sure were lots of them.
I remember loving Smallville.
The people, the community,
how the small things were
the big things.
And I thought I'd live there forever.
Dad? Dad! Dad...
Dad, wake up! Somebody call 911!
But my father's death
set me on a different path.
Eventually I moved to Metropolis...
to become who I was meant to be.
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [CRASHING]
[THUDDING]
Here you go, friend.
Thanks. Cool costume.
Thanks. My mom made it for me.
But my most vivid memory of all
was the day I met her.
[MAN] Everyone in here,
we're the most dependable friends
the people of Metropolis have.
- You remember that.
- Yes, sir.
Stick with Lane.
She'll show you the ropes.
Lane, sir?
Who told you to wear a tie?
Let me guess, Lombard? Ignore him.
Though, he can get box seats
to the Meteors. You like baseball?
Of course. I mean, who doesn't like
America's pastime, Miss Lane?
It's Lois. What did you say
your name was again?
Kent. Clark. Clark Kent.
Oh! Oh.
Sorry.
Hmm.
I've never met a Clark before.
Oh, uh...
I've never met a Lois before.
Actually, there was my first
grade teacher, Lois Hannigan.
So, I guess technically...
Technically, you'd be the second...
We fell in love.
I told Lois who I really was,
where I came from.
[WHOOPING]
[CLARK] We married,
got our first place together.
The twins came.
They were as different as brothers get.
Jonathan was easy,
always happy, always smiling.
[CHEERING]
[LOIS] Good job, babe.
[CLAPPING]
[CLARK] Things with Jordan
were more challenging.
Tantrums, night terrors.
A year ago, he was diagnosed
with social anxiety disorder.
And suddenly here I am
living in Metropolis,
raising two teenage boys,
married to the most famous
journalist in the world.
Trying to make the world safer
for the people I love.
[HELICOPTER FLYING]
[SIREN WAILING]
Here, here. Here.
Hey, hey, hey. How long we got
before this thing pops its top?
A few minutes tops.
- Fallout?
- As far as Metropolis.
Come on, Superman.
- [WOMAN] The heat exchanger's offline.
- [MAN] Where's the damn water tanker?
[MAN 2]
His cold breath isn't going to fix it.
[WOMAN 2]
We need water back in the reactor vessel
or we're going to have a meltdown
the size of Fukushima.
- [MAN 2] A lot of water!
- [MAN 3] Tanks!
[ICE HARDENING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
It's cooling down.
[CROWD GASPS]
[CHEERING AND WHOOPING]
It's just like Oyster Creek.
Same kind of crack in the cooling tower.
How is it no one
at either plant saw anything?
I don't know yet.
But you can't get equipment
in here unnoticed.
- Both cracks were man-made.
- That's what concerns me.
You've been putting in a lot
of OT lately.
My daughter okay with that?
She's not the one I have to worry about.
Bass are going to start biting
again soon.
Was thinking I'd take Jonathan fishing,
maybe even get Jordan to come this time.
I'll talk to Lois about some dates.
Good night, General.
[WHOOSHING]
And the delivery truck
crashed into your car?
[WOMAN TALKS INDISTINCTLY ON PHONE]
It was an unmarked box truck?
Can you hold on one sec?
I've gotta get Foswell copy
first thing in the morning.
- Okay.
- Your plate's in the fridge.
Jonathan's got some news,
and apologize to Jordan.
You missed therapy today.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
[GIRL]
How do you know she is with...
- Come in.
- You've never met her.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey!
- Mom said you had news?
- Eliza, one second.
Yeah, yeah. I'm actually starting QB.
- For varsity?
- Yep.
Yeah.
I think I'm the first freshman
to ever do it.
And some of the upper classmen
are pretty ticked off.
Don't worry about them.
Worry? No, it's awesome.
You should have seen their faces.
Um... Dad.
Oh. Right. Yeah. Okay, okay.
- Hi, Eliza.
- Hi.
- Hey, congrats.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Proud of you.
- Okay, thanks.
- Okay, I'm outta here.
- Thanks. All right.
[MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY]
Hey!
[TURNS DOWN MUSIC]
Wow. You make a pretty good Superman.
Superman's boring. I'm Raiden.
Huh. Um...
I'm sorry I, uh,
missed our therapy today, um...
I was in Wichita for a story.
You couldn't catch a flight back,
Mom said.
So, uh, high school starts tomorrow.
You nervous? Because, you know,
it's okay if you're nervous.
I know freshman year
was pretty tough for me.
Did I ever tell you about the time
I was the team manager of the...
Everyone duct taped you
to a tractor, yeah.
Life's little different in Smallville
than it is in Metropolis.
Okay, well, you know, if you...
If you need anything,
if you want to talk,
I'm here.
[SCREAMING]
Hey, Dad.
Yeah.
The music?
Right.
[TURNS MUSIC UP]
I saw you on the news.
Are you just getting home now?
Yeah, uh... Got home a little bit ago.
Honey, I know you've got
a lot on your plate,
but you really do need
to be around more.
Mom, I do have a responsibility
to the world, as you know who.
Well, you've got a bigger responsibility
to your family, as a father.
The boys need to see what a strong and
loving and vulnerable man looks like.
What your father was to you.
You only have them
for a short while longer
before they go off into the world.
You've got to be present.
I'm trying.
I really am.
I don't want to let anybody down.
Was it, um...
Was it always this hard for you and Dad?
Your lives are so much more complicated
than ours ever were.
Besides, life's a little different
in Smallville, remember?
[GROANS]
You okay?
I just need to lie down, that's all.
Get some sleep, Mom.
Love you.
Good night, honey.
Good night.
[SIZZLING]
- Get 'em while they're hot.
- Thanks.
- More juice?
- I think I'm good. Thank you.
Little help?
Your mom called while you were
in the shower about a visit.
- Are we going to Grandma's?
- I think we're overdue.
Great, Smallville.
A place where you can spend
a full year in one afternoon.
It's not that bad.
Wow. Is that how
you're going dressed today?
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Somebody got the
punch-me-in the-face memo.
I should dress like you? Like some sort
of human participation trophy?
No, but you could watch a, like,
how-to basic video on style.
Enough. Both of you, go,
your ride's here.
Bye.
- I love you, guys.
- Love you.
- Good luck today, guys.
- Thanks, Dad.
You're worried about Jordan.
I tried talking to him last night,
but he was pretty upset.
If he knew where you really were...
Your parents told you about
your real heritage when you were six.
But that was different.
I lived on a farm. I had powers.
You don't think Jonathan's
got something?
Tests at the fortress
said that it was unlikely.
He's about to be starting quarterback
at one of most competitive
high schools in the nation
as a freshman.
Yeah. Doesn't mean he has powers.
Have you seen him throw a deep route?
And what about Jordan?
All it's gonna do is make him feel
more alien than he already does.
Trust me, I've been there.
We're late.
- It's too dangerous for them to know.
- It's more dangerous if they don't.
Lois, they slip up once,
say the wrong thing to one person,
the whole world knows who I am.
What?
- Your father agrees with me.
- Now we care what my dad thinks?
I'm just saying. They're 14,
they don't need to know yet.
Maxy, what's going on?
Troupe. Fired.
More layoffs? I knew when Morgan Edge
bought the Planet, there'd be cuts,
but this is unbelievable.
Kent, you got a minute?
Foswell fired you?
Look, it's better me
than somebody else, okay?
- I do have another day job.
- That's not the point.
Foswell's no editor.
He's a patsy for Edge.
All these billionaires
that buy media outlets
use this moving-to-digital crap
as an excuse to destroy journalism.
They don't care about
human interest stories or facts.
All they care about is click-throughs.
Ow!
You're gonna need a new excuse
for being gone all the time now.
- Lois, we're not telling the boys.
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Mom. Sorry.
This morning's just been...
Dr. Frye?
Clark.
How did you...
The stroke...
It...
[SNIFFLING]
[MINISTER]
Faithful God, Lord of all creation.
The desire that nothing redeemed
by your son will ever be lost
as we return the ashes
of our sister to the Earth
to live with you and all your children
forever and ever.
Amen.
[MARTHA] Clark!
What's that?
It's one o'clock, don't you need
to take your pill or something?
What are you? Mom?
Someone's got to watch out for you.
Clark here and his dad,
they could harvest crops
faster than any farm in the area.
How's your place, Mr. Branden?
We had to sell to Oberlee Foods
last year.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
It's hard for family farmers to make it
around here nowadays.
[WOMAN HEARD WITH SUPER-HEARING]
It's been so long since we've seen him.
Come on, kids, keep up.
Remember that girl
from that summer we stayed here?
- Sarah Cushing?
- Yeah.
She's here.
Really, where?
Fifty yards and approaching.
If you hurry, you'll have time
to go inside and change
into a completely different person.
Clark, I'm so sorry.
She was always so kind to me.
To all of us.
- It's good to see you, Lana.
- Same.
Lois, great to see you. I'm sorry
it's under these circumstances.
It's nice to see you, too.
You remember our boys?
Jonathan and Jordan.
- Hi.
- Hey.
These are our girls.
The littlest one here is Sophie.
And the one
with the perma-scowl over there,
- that's Sarah.
- Dad.
I'm really sorry about your grandma.
She was really special.
Even my dad liked her,
and he hates everyone, so...
[JONATHAN CHUCKLES]
House full of girls.
Someone's always pissed at you.
- [SOPHIE] Mommy.
- [LANA] Mmm-hmm.
That's him.
Well, your daddy and I went
to high school with Mr. Kent.
You dated him.
That's why Daddy got mad
when he saw you on his Facebook page.
Okay, sweets, why don't you go play?
Oh...
How are you holding up?
I could really use a drink, actually.
Now you're talking. Lead the way.
I didn't think you guys would have
remembered me from that summer.
Of course we would. I mean...
But you changed your... Everything.
What my brother's trying to say
is that whatever you're doing is...
It's totally working for you.
Well, we still get puberty
in Smallville.
Although, cell service sucks, so...
You know, I've been trying
to get on all morning.
I think there's something
wrong with the router.
Just probably needs to be reset.
Jon, it's in the barn.
Mysterious. What's in the barn?
Our dad doesn't like us in there.
He says it's full of stuff
that can kill us.
Yeah, when we were, like, eight.
Well, as a member of the FFA,
I think I can keep you guys safe.
- What's the FFA?
- I don't know.
[LOIS]
Your daughters are so gorgeous.
[LANA] Oh, thank you.
And you look exactly the same
as you did in high school.
He doesn't age.
It's good genes, I guess.
And, Lois, I read all your stories.
It's so impressive.
Because of you,
I tell my girls they can do anything.
Thank you. Are you still at the bank?
Yeah. And Kyle's still at the firehouse,
made fire chief last year,
and everybody else we know moved away.
She means bailed.
- Lueck?
- Twin Cities.
- Sippy?
- St. Louis.
Maybe you'll see them at
the next reunion.
Kent didn't make it
to the last one now, did he?
I was supposed to but...
You know, it used to be that when
folks move away to get their degrees
well, they bring their skills back home,
take care of the community
that's helped raise them, you know?
But that ain't happening anymore.
Hey, we'll at least get a lifeline
if this whole Edge proposal
goes through, right?
What does Morgan Edge
want with Smallville?
- Oh, boy.
- He's retrofitting the coal mines
to produce alternative energies.
He's gonna put a lot of folks
back to work around here.
- Until it doesn't.
- [CLARK] Lois...
Morgan Edge ruins everything he touches.
What's he ruined?
He is single-handedly destroying
the Daily Planet.
People quit reading that paper
because you reporters
can't keep the politics to yourselves.
Edge's companies prey
on struggling communities.
He busts up unions.
He barely pays a living wage.
I don't understand
how he can keep fooling people.
You mean us dumb, backward,
small-town folk?
No, no, that is not what I meant.
I know what you meant.
See, people like you,
you look at Smallville
and you think of the past
and you feel real bad for us, right?
People like Morgan Edge, though...
Now, see, he looks at Smallville,
and he sees the future.
It's not a future
I would want to live in.
It's good thing we don't have to worry
about that anymore now, do we?
We haven't made any decisions
about the farm yet, Kyle.
But your mother has.
What does that mean?
Kyle, go get the girls.
I'm sorry for your loss, Kent.
Evening.
Lana, what's he talking about?
Your mother had
some business with us, that's all.
Come by the bank tomorrow.
Martha was a great lady.
The heart of Smallville, really.
I'm sorry she's gone.
[SARAH] Yeah, your dad's right.
Pretty much everything
here can kill you.
- What's that thing?
- That's a hay raker.
I guess you guys don't see
much of this in Metropolis.
No, but our dad told us all
these stories about growing up here.
Did he tell you it sucks?
Actually, I think he kind of loved it.
Of course.
It can't be that bad. I mean,
it's more the people
that make up a place, right?
Wow.
Metropolis boys are really starting
to lose their game.
Relax, I'm taken.
I didn't mean it like that.
I'm just saying...
Well, I guess I'm trying to say
that we're only here for a few days
and I figured that we kind of need
someone to show us around.
Mmm.
Okay. Phone.
Oh no, not you.
You.
Thank you, uh...
There's a bonfire tomorrow
at the old Shuster Mine.
Hit me up if you want to go,
but I can't guarantee
I won't get you
into a little bit of trouble.
- Guys, found the router.
- [ALL CHUCKLE]
What the hell was Grandma thinking
putting it up there?
I got it.
Oh. Jordan, be careful.
"Come by the bank?"
Wonder what that was all about.
I shouldn't have lost my cool with Kyle.
You think he's right?
Should I have come back
to Smallville more often?
No, Clark, he's not right.
Your mom knew where you were
and who you were.
Right before she died, I...
I heard her say something
as I was flying here.
It's time to come home.
She wanted me to come home.
I just don't know why yet.
[CREAKING]
Careful.
- It's still not working.
- Got it.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING AND COUGHING]
[LOUD CLATTER]
Oh, my God.
[SARAH] Help! Somebody help!
The boys, they're hurt!
[LOIS] Go get medical supplies.
It was his idea.
It's okay.
You're saying all we have
are mild concussions?
You're both really lucky.
[PARAMEDIC]
A little rest, you should be fine.
- Thanks, Benny. It's good to see you.
- Yeah.
- No worries, thank you.
- Best to the family.
- Thank you. I'm sorry for your loss.
- Thanks.
Come on, boys. Let's get upstairs.
You've had a long day.
Great, Engstrom just said
that I might not be starting anymore
because I missed practice all week.
Seriously? Football's what
you're worried about right now?
How are we fine, Jon?
Jordan, look, if you want to fixate
on something weird,
maybe you should start thinking about
how Sarah Cushing
gave you her digits and not me.
You texted here already, didn't you?
I don't know. What...
I just wanted her to know
we were okay, all right?
What is this?
You sent a waving hand emoji?
No, that is a Vulcan salute.
I got to say that's...
That's even worse.
Kind of a freak.
You know what?
Something a lot freakier than me
happened to us in that barn.
Something we're not being told about.
And it's up to us
to find out what that is.
Okay. Whatever, weirdo.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Jonathan must have somehow
shielded them both?
You saw how confused they are.
They need to know the truth.
What's the truth gonna do to Jordan?
It's hard enough on him having a brother
that everything comes easy to.
But having one that has powers
like Superman?
We don't know what he can
or can't do yet.
And yes, it will be hard for him,
but he will have his family there
to help him figure things out,
like he does right now.
I can't lose him, Lois.
I can't.
He's pulled so far away from me already.
When we were dreaming
about having a family,
it didn't look like this, did it?
Didn't have lost jobs
or teens with severe anxiety
or parents gone too soon.
No one ever dreams about the problems,
but every life has them,
even the extraordinary ones.
[WOMAN]
Sitrep on the way, General.
Your dad's back.
That's not good.
[GENERAL LANE] Had my team analyze
security camera footage
from both nuclear plants
where the ruptures occurred,
and this is the only commonality.
- Whatever did this, it's moving fast.
- That's not all.
We also discovered
a sub-microscopic etching at both sites.
Thought maybe it was
a fingerprint at first.
It wasn't.
It's Kryptonian.
"You are not a hero, Kal-El."
- Whoever did this knows who I am.
- He's studying you, Clark.
I'm sure there's a phone booth in this
podunk town where you can suit up.
[LOIS] Now? No.
Lois...
I get it. There is a powerful
something out there
that doesn't like Superman
or nuclear power plants
and that is a bad combo.
But now is not a moment
Clark can just take off.
His mom just died.
I mean it, Clark.
The world will always need Superman.
And when there is a problem,
you will be there for them.
But right now,
this family needs you more.
She's right, Sam.
- I tried to warn you, Lois.
- Dad, not this again.
When you wanted to get married,
I tried warning you.
You may have fallen in love
with Clark Kent,
but you married Superman.
And Superman doesn't get
to have a normal life,
no matter how much you want one for him
or yourself.
[LANA] How are the boys doing?
They're fine.
They're just a little shaken up.
[SIGHS]
It seems luck runs in the family.
Did Clark ever tell you
about our accident
coming home from a Soul Asylum concert?
I try not to talk about
my Soul Asylum days too much.
[LANA CHUCKLES]
So, Pete was at the wheel,
fell asleep, drove off the road,
when we came to, the car was a pretzel.
Nobody was hurt. Not a scratch.
It was the strangest thing.
Then again, lots of strange things
happened here back then.
Okay...
Mortgage papers?
- My mom paid hers off years ago.
- Her first.
About five years ago,
at the peak of the farming crisis,
banks here were offering
reverse mortgages to seniors.
Pay now for the opportunity
to let the bank purchase
the remainder of the farm
upon their death,
if the landowner's heirs couldn't repay
the balance of the loan.
She didn't need that kind of money.
No, but the Gordons
were gonna be evicted
from their farm that had been
in their family for generations.
Margie Kelton's lung surgery made it so
she could hardly put food on the table.
I have dozens of stories.
Everyone in town knew
that if you were in trouble,
Martha would be there.
She was like your friend
you always write about, Lois.
She was like this town's Superman
or Superwoman.
It sounds like they had a lot in common.
She still protected half
the farm's value.
She wanted there to be enough money
to send the boys to college.
So, you can either repay the loan
or you can accept a healthy buyout
for the remaining value of the property.
You really think
Dad's hiding something from us?
We had all those poles land on us.
Besides, how did he get 'em
up off of us so fast, anyway?
I don't know, adrenaline maybe?
Like soccer mom lifting a car,
kind of thing.
Dad can't put up a Christmas tree
without falling off the ladder.
And what's the thing he says
every single time we come here?
"Don't put your finger in that?"
I don't know.
"Stay out of the barn," dumbass.
Jordan, what are we looking for anyways?
Something unusual,
something out of place.
- What?
- You hear that?
The poles,
they must have shifted the floor.
I think it's a door.
Look, look, look.
Three, two, one.
Help me with this.
[METAL CLANKING]
- Get the flashlight.
- Yeah.
This is literally just an old cellar.
It's probably Grandpa's
old tool storage or something.
Jon.
All right.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What is that thing?
What are you doing? Do not touch that.
Oh, my God.
Did you see that?
What the hell was that?
No, no, no, no.
What was that? Jordan? What was that?
Jordan, what are you...
What the hell is that thing?
Whatever it is, it's not from Kansas.
All my memories,
my childhood, my parents,
they're all here.
Why would my mom want me
to come home just to sell the farm?
I don't think she wanted you to sell it.
I think she wanted you to save it.
How?
We're not exactly flush with cash,
especially after getting fired.
I don't know yet,
but those reverse mortgages
weren't because the bank
was feeling generous.
You may have super strength
and super hearing,
but I have super smell,
and those loans don't smell right.
- I do have super smell, by the way.
- [CHUCKLES]
I just don't use it very often,
you know?
Not with two teenage boys in the house.
Kinda gross.
Two very upset teenage boys.
So, that's why? That's why
you never wanted us in the barn?
Because you keep
a freaking alien ship in there.
- Look I can explain.
- Yeah, can you?
Can you explain how we fell 30 feet
and nothing happened?
- Just give him a chance.
- All you said is that we got lucky,
but that was a lie, wasn't it?
Yes. Yes, okay? It was a lie.
Look, that ship brought me to Earth.
I landed here in Smallville,
right in those cornfields over there.
I was sent here when my planet,
Krypton, was destroyed.
- Krypton?
- Yes.
And because I wasn't from here,
I had certain powers.
Your grandparents, they took me in.
They raised me.
Taught me how to control my abilities,
how to blend in,
until the day I was ready to leave
and become who I was sent here to be.
You're saying you're Superman?
No, I've seen Superman before.
We've seen him.
When your father first told me,
I didn't understand either.
I understand.
[CAR THUDDING]
I understand all the excuses.
All the times you were gone.
You lied to us.
- You both did.
- He was saving lives, Jordan.
That doesn't make it less true.
You lied to protect his secret.
All the things I've been feeling.
You made me think I was crazy.
They put me on pills.
Your mental health has nothing to do
- with who your father is.
- And how do you know that?
I'm half human,
half whatever the hell he is.
Do not yell at your mother. Okay?
This is not her fault.
I'm the one that didn't
want you to know.
- Why?
- Because I knew what kind of burden
it would be if you both had powers.
Or worse, if one of you had them
and the other one didn't.
You think he's the reason
we survived yesterday.
- What are you talking about?
- Go on, Dad.
Go and tell Superboy here
why he's really so perfect.
We thought your athletic talents
could be latent abilities
starting to emerge, and then yesterday...
The only way that both of you
survived that accident
is for at least one of
you to be like me.
Wouldn't have it any other way,
would you, Dad?
Jordan.
Don't try to talk to me, all right?
You may have been sent here
to be some hero,
but you sure as hell weren't
sent here to be a father.
Just leave us alone.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Everything I do with the boys just
seems like it blows up in my face.
Is Jordan right?
Am I a bad father?
- Clark...
- 'Cause right now
it feels like it's my fault
that this is all falling apart.
Your life falling apart
doesn't mean you're special,
it means you're human.
[HEARING INDISTINCT VOICES]
[WOMAN]
Temperature reaching critical meltdown.
It's another nuclear facility.
Hey.
We're gonna be all right, okay?
Go.
I found your message.
- I know you're here.
- [MAN] And I know you can't see me.
Lead encasements.
You can't see through lead.
It's one of your few weaknesses.
So, that's why you're choosing
nuclear facilities.
You could watch me without me knowing.
And see how good you really are, Kal-El.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Sarah.
Hey, you made it. See you guys later.
I still don't understand
how you guys didn't get hurt.
Still figuring that one out.
Well, I'm just glad that you made it.
You promised me trouble.
Well, I will definitely do my best.
I don't really know how
you guys party in Metropolis,
but here in Smallville,
we do it a little different.
How do you know my name?
[MAN] I know everything there is to know
about the last son of Krypton.
Where I come from, let's just say
the two of us have history.
And where is that exactly?
Nowhere now.
My world was destroyed,
but somehow I managed to survive.
I eventually arrived here,
where I learned you were here, too.
You're not as fast as I thought.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe you shouldn't.
Beer and benzos don't really mix well.
How'd you know?
I saw you take one back
at the funeral reception.
But you're not the only one,
you know, on something, so...
You, for what?
We really gonna do this now?
Go full Euphoria on each other.
We don't have to.
You're just kind of
the only person I know around here.
No, it's cool. Come on.
Up until I was
11 or 12,
I had a pretty awesome life.
I mean, it wasn't perfect,
but it was nice.
Dolls and dance classes.
But then something changed.
People around here,
they get this sadness,
and they act like it's something
you can catch, like the flu,
but I never thought
it was gonna hit my house till it did.
Now, half the nights,
my dad sleeps on the couch.
And my mom gets really mad at him
for being checked out,
but honestly, I can't blame him.
He's a firefighter.
And being a firefighter here,
you see all the really bad stuff.
I mean, stuff that no one
really wants to talk about.
Like what?
Like, parents cooking meth
and the whole house catching on fire
with their kids inside.
Anyways,
about a year ago,
I took a bunch of my mom's pills.
I still don't understand why I did it.
I've never done anything
like that before.
And my mom,
she made a really big drama out of it.
Lots of therapy and whatever.
I know, for a... For a sad story,
it's really basic.
No, it's not.
What are you doing?
- What?
- Hey!
- Sean!
- That's my girlfriend!
- Sean, what the hell is your problem?
- What are you doing with this guy?
- It doesn't even matter. Relax, relax.
- Girlfriend?
I would have gotten around to it,
but you sort of kissed me first.
- And it's not that big of a deal.
- Back off!
What the hell are you doing?
You know how many townies
I had to randomly DM to find out
- where this party was?
- Out of the way!
Back off!
You really don't want
to get in my face right now.
[SHOUTING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Aren't you curious how I know
so much about you, Kal-El?
Like me, your home was destroyed.
You were sent here as an infant,
to world where you'd spend your whole
life trying to prove your worth.
Convince yourself you were one of them.
But you're not!
You're still that scared, lost child,
desperate for the love of people
that will never accept you.
And the only remnants
of your real home, kryptonite,
make you sick.
[GRUNTS]
Dust to dust, Superman.
Yeah.
You still got those contacts at HUD?
I need you to check
Smallville Community Bank
for any unusual activity
in the last five
- or six years.
- [REPORTER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
...it is a volatile situation
for firefighters...
Maxy, I gotta go.
[WHIRRING]
Clark?
Who told you to wear a tie?
Clark, come home.
[GRUNTS]
[SIRENS]
Dad.
Jonathan.
[KYLE] The other one's pretty shook up.
Twice in two days, Kent.
Luckiest family I know.
Kyle.
Thank you.
- Hey, are you all right? What happened?
- Dad. Dad,
I'm okay, but Jordan...
[LOIS]
So, you saved your brother.
I wasn't sure what happened.
That's why I didn't say anything.
All I knew is, when I fell,
I felt something come over me.
A strength I've never had before. I felt
control.
I don't know. It's hard to explain.
What's gonna happen to him?
I'm not sure yet.
Jordan's powers are manifesting
very differently than mine did.
But we're gonna
help you get through this. Okay?
Yeah, it's probably like
learning to drive a car, you know,
if cars were indestructible and
had giant death lasers as headlights.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Apologize to your brother.
I know. Too soon, I know.
You were right.
Should've told him a long time ago.
Jordan could've killed someone tonight.
We just got to be
on the same page going forward.
[MARTHA]
These are the important years, Clark.
Life's a little different in Smallville.
I think I know what my mom meant
when she said to come home.
She knew how busy we are in Metropolis,
how absent I've been.
I've tried convincing myself
that the boys would be fine,
and that it was okay
for me to be gone so much.
But I was wrong.
You think your mom wanted us to move
to Smallville and live on the farm?
It's a simpler life.
More time with each other,
be part of a community. And now this.
I think she felt like this
family needs Smallville.
As much as the world needs Superman?
Look, I know.
I know it would be a huge,
huge change.
Yeah, it would.
But I think she was right.
Really?
You know, I think about my dad a lot.
He was just heading off
to church one day
when a meteor crashed in his front yard.
And just like that,
he was a father.
I didn't know it back then,
but he had no idea what he was doing.
That didn't matter
'cause he was always there.
You were right.
I haven't always been there for you.
But I promise you, from now on,
I will be.
[LANA] I pulled some strings.
Got you $2,100 an acre,
which is well above market value
in Rice County.
Wow, that... That's very generous.
Um...
But we decided we're...
We're not selling.
You're not?
We're thinking of reopening the farm,
and run it the way my folks and I
used to back in the day.
So, you're staying?
Well, we're talking it over, but
a change might be good for this family.
Okay.
Then, let's go over
the pre-negotiated terms
for taking on the loan.
Before we do, Lana,
I was wondering if you knew
that a couple months before
those reverse mortgages were offered,
a company had secretly
acquired your bank.
No, I didn't know that.
Galaxy Holdings, whose majority
shareholder is Morgan Edge.
Why would someone like Morgan Edge
be interested in a bunch
of family farms in Smallville, Kansas?
That's a very good question.
How's everyone doing after last night?
Tag Harris broke his arm.
Other than that, nobody else got hurt.
Anyone say what caused the explosion?
My dad said it was probably
just a methane pocket.
Look, I should have never
kissed you last night.
Wow. That is awkward. Good luck.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know about Sean,
and I'm just really sorry
about how it all went down.
I just wanted to hang out with you.
You were so sweet that summer
that we met.
And then, yeah, I saw you
take the pill at the funeral and...
I just thought that
if someone like you had issues,
then someone like me wasn't
so messed up.
I think maybe it means
we're both just a little messed up.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Do you think that
you can keep it a secret?
Well, one person finds out,
and then everybody knows,
- and then just...
- Yeah. Yeah, you don't...
Your secret's safe with me.
- Thanks.
- Sarah!
- I'm sorry.
- It's... It's all right.
- See you around?
- Yeah.
Well, that didn't look
like a total disaster.
- Am I right?
- Yeah. Look...
Jon, about the powers.
It's all good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Powers are overrated anyways.
Plus, this just
confirms what I've known
to be true all along.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
My skills on the field are legit.
Come on.
I still cannot believe
you just said that to her.
You know, when you first...
Hey, boys?
What would you guys think about
staying here a little longer
than any of us planned?
Like a couple days or something?
More like permanently?
I mean, I have school,
practice with the team...
We know. We know.
It's a big conversation.
Yeah, we'll have it tonight
at family dinner.
We just wanted to give you both
some time to process
what this would really be like
before we do.
Okay.
Until then, you two,
follow me out to the barn.
I wanna show you a few things.
Like, Superman things?
Like, how to attach a plow to a tractor.
- What?
- Seriously?
Those fields aren't
gonna plough themselves.
Okay, but, Dad, we have questions.
- We just found out our dad's Superman.
- I got, like,
thousands and thousands of questions...
We need to improve tactile function
and speed if I'm gonna end this.
[FEMALE VOICE] We also need kryptonite.
That was the last of your supply.
[MAN] Then we'll have to go get some.
I'll start the upgrades
to your armor right away,
Captain Luthor.